<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Birthday Info</string>
    <string name="app_name2">B. Info</string>
    <string name="data">Date of born</string>
    <string name="dob">Date of Born</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="calc">Calculates age</string>
    <string name="data_n">Date of born</string>
    <string name="hour">Hour</string>
    <string name="cal">Today</string>
    <string name="calcul">Calculate</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome on</string>
    <string name="welcome2">Welcome on</string>
    <string name="age">Your age</string>
    <string name="age2">Statistics of your age</string>
    <string name="month">Total Months</string>
    <string name="sett">Total Weeks</string>
    <string name="gg">Total Days</string>
    <string name="ore">Total Hours</string>
    <string name="min">Minute</string>
    <string name="sec">Seconds</string>
    <string name="news">More news/events on your date of birth</string>
    <string name="accadde">Historical events\nin your birthday</string>
    <string name="oroscopo">View the horoscope</string>
    <string name="close">Close the page</string>
    <string name="Registrati">Recorded</string>
    <string name="binfo">BIRTHDAY INFO</string>
    <string name="info">Curious or curious about having your birthday info? Well you are in
        right place....</string>
    <string name="info2">... First, write your name and last name, then indicate whether you are a man or a woman and have a lot of fun with
        Birthday Info.</string>
    <string name="info3">You will then have news about your age and curiosity on your birthday and also know about your personal horoscope !!!</string>
    <string name = "man_woman"> Are You Woman or Man? </string>
    <string name = "details"> Click here if you want to know more </string>
    <string name = "netx_"> Your next birthday is between </string>
    <string name = "c_zod"> Chinese Zodiac </string>
    <string name = "mayan"> Zodiac Maya </string>
    <string name = "day"> Birth Day </string>
    <string name = "h_zod"> Zodiac sign </string>
    <string name = "chinese"> Chinese Zodiac </string>
    <string name = "prossimi"> Upcoming Birthday </string>
    <string name = "about"> Info </string>
    <string name = "other"> Other Apps </string>
    <string name = "celtic"> Celtic horoscope </string>
    <string name = "c_m"> Zodiac Maya </string>
    <string name = "c_c"> Celtic Horoscope </string>
    <string name = "netx_b"> Upcoming birthdays </string>
    <string name="indietro">Go back</string>
    <string name="earth">Age of Earth when you were born</string>
    <string name="celtic_month">Celtic calendar month</string>
    <string name="credits">Image by\nhttp://www.dossier.net/relax/zodiaco_cinese/\nit.freepik.com
    \nwww.wijkipedia.it\nDamon Hellanbrand\n\nHappy Birthday animation by Copyright 2015 The Android Open Source Project, Inc.</string>
    <string name="sign">Your sign</string>
    <string name="next_text">NEXT</string>
    <string name="version">Version 1.3</string>
    <string name="name">Insert your name</string>
    <string name="cognome">Insert your surname</string>
    <string name="year">years</string>
    <string name="months">months</string>
    <string name="dayss">days</string>
    <string name="mouse">Mouse</string>
    <string name="tigre">Tiger</string>
    <string name="drago">Dragon</string>
    <string name="cavallo">Horse</string>
    <string name="cane">Dog</string>
    <string name="bufalo">Bufalo</string>
    <string name="lepre">Hare</string>
    <string name="serpente">Snake</string>
    <string name="scimmia">Monkey</string>
    <string name="gallo">Cock</string>
    <string name="capra">Goat</string>
    <string name="gnu">Gnu</string>
    <string name="cinghiale">Pig</string>
    <string name="ariete">Aries</string>
    <string name="toro">Bull</string>
    <string name="gemelli">Twins</string>
    <string name="cancro">Cancer</string>
    <string name="leone">Lion</string>
    <string name="vergine">Virgin</string>
    <string name="bilancia">Wheitscale</string>
    <string name="scorpione">Scorpion</string>
    <string name="saggittario">Sagittarius</string>
    <string name="capricorno">Capricorn</string>
    <string name="acquario">Acquarium</string>
    <string name="pesci">Fishes</string>
    <string name="lucertola">Kibray</string>
    <string name="scimmia_m">Ratz</string>
    <string name="falcone">Coz</string>
    <string name="giaguaro">Balam</string>
    <string name="cane_m">Pek</string>
    <string name="serpente_m">Kan</string>
    <string name="lepre_m">Tzaub</string>
    <string name="tartaruga">Aak</string>
    <string name="pipi">Tzootz</string>
    <string name="scorpione_m">Dzec</string>
    <string name="cervo">Keh</string>
    <string name="civetta">Moan</string>
    <string name="pavone">Kutz</string>
    <string name="abete">Fir</string>
    <string name="acero">Maple</string>
    <string name="betulla">Birch</string>
    <string name="carpino">Hornbeam</string>
    <string name="castagno">Chestnaut</string>
    <string name="cedro">Cedar</string>
    <string name="cipresso">Cypress</string>
    <string name="corniolo">Dogwood</string>
    <string name="faggio">Beech</string>
    <string name="fico">Ficus</string>
    <string name="frassino">Ash Tree</string>
    <string name="melo">Melo</string>
    <string name="nocciolo">Hazel</string>
    <string name="noce">Hazel</string>
    <string name="olmo">Elm</string>
    <string name="pino">Pine</string>
    <string name="pioppo">Poplar</string>
    <string name="quercia">Oak</string>
    <string name="salice">Willow</string>
    <string name="tiglio">Lime</string>
    <string name="ulivo">Olive</string>
    <string name="gen">Jenuary</string>
    <string name="feb">Febraury</string>
    <string name="mar">March</string>
    <string name="apr">April</string>
    <string name="mag">May</string>
    <string name="giu">June</string>
    <string name="lug">July</string>
    <string name="ago">August</string>
    <string name="set">September</string>
    <string name="ott">October</string>
    <string name="nov">November</string>
    <string name="dic">Dicember</string>
    <string name="horror">Horror</string>
    <string name="zodi">Zodiach</string>
    <string name="all">All</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="material">Material</string>
    <string name="normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="scuro">Dark</string>
    <string name="view">View Birthday</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello</string>
    <string name="ops">Oops...</string>
    <string name="error_data">The date of birth must be less than or equal to today\'s date!</string>
    <string name="melo2">Melo</string>
    <string name="mouse_s"> The Tops are born of a great charisma, which favors and facilitates their ties of sincere and deep friendship. Even in the couple\'s life this quality gives them the opportunity to join a companion worthy of them, and equally eager to enjoy those same joys and satisfactions that the Mouse likes and rarely renounces. The Topo is endowed with tremendous patience and lucidity, even in facing the toughest tests; Often this quality leads him to quickly achieve success, and his career advancements, in his professional field. The desire to widen its own physical and mental horizons drives him to love traveling and to experience the novelties; In this way it is first rather anticonformist and then, with the passing of years, more responsible. At times, the Slain is a sinner of pride: the most important thing to look at is arrogance, the belief in others above, without giving them the opportunity to express themselves. </string>
    <string name="cow_s"> Bufal\'s births are characterized by an exemplary patience, which in their case is rarely put to the test: they have a very high level of oppression. However, when the limit is exceeded, they may lose control completely. In their work they are particularly meticulous and fussy; Trouble asking them to divert attention from what they are devoting for whatever reason. They are able to achieve important results thanks to a serious and precise situation analysis capabilities; This also allows them to play roles prevailing in the interior of important working environments. The mistake that they may incur is that of monotony, that is to say, never to be unpredictable or minimally conciliatory to what is unconventional. </string>
    <string name="tigre_s"> The Tigers born are of great charisma, which helps them to easily obtain and cling to power positions; Thanks to this remarkable quality, they are also facilitated in human relationships. And this is why they often engage in politics successfully, but sometimes at the risk of overestimating themselves and their potentialities. They usually enjoy a great deal of luck in the game. The mistake that the Tiger\'s birth can cause is that they are sometimes unpleasant; This is because of excessive determination, which forces them to never surrender in the course of a challenge. They may also suffer from mood swings. </string>
    <string name="cavallo_s"> Horse borns have a fervent social life, which often animate themselves thanks to their team-mate\'s skills. Abilities in conversation and generous compliments to others give the friends friends happy and carefree. They also have great insight and understanding about the ideas of others. Their most fragile side is identified with the uncertainty, the loss of their security, which sometimes manifest without warning. The mistake they may incur is to be too loquacious, with the risk of annoying someone who is close to them. </string>
    <string name="gnu_s"> Goat\'s births are endemic and inventive, but may remain unproductive in the absence of someone who can advise on the direction to take. This help is also indispensable for achieving, in the workplace, in gratifications, and even financials. Their creativity is not a lonely quality, but it is flanked by a strong altruism: giving without asking for anything in return is what the Goat\'s people love to do. In the life of a couple, they are usually fond of the relationship on firm bases of honesty and loyalty; In this way they live long relationships over time, without feeling the need for any evasion. The mistake that Goat\'s birth can cause is to lose hope of achieving the prefetted results already at the first difficulty. </string>
    <string name="gallo_s"> The Cock\'s births are provided with pragmatism and concreteness, which affine their spirit of observation. For them, every tool can be the right one, as long as you achieve your goals. In the relationship with others they use the frankness that sets them apart with snout for business and acumen; All these qualities push them straight to achieving success. Their friends are not numerous, but in them the Cock\'s birth are all trust; In turn, are willing to do anything to help them. They have merits and defects in equal amounts; Among them are excessive meticulousness, extreme desire to regain after an overwhelming, attention focused primarily on their own needs. </string>
    <string name="lepre_s">Hare\'s natives have a dowry, altruism, which allows them to conquer the affection and consideration of people without fatigue. In couple\'s life they are very tender and sentimental; Many times their relationship with their partner is almost mythical. Not to feel uncomfortable, they need to spend most of their time in family circles; For this reason they prefer to avoid long journeys. True happiness is ensured by the presence of the family, and the sense of stability that it guarantees. The mistake in which the Hare\'s nests are more easily transmitted is to see everything with veiled eyes of negativity; Are tendentially pessimistic. Sometimes Lepre is identified with the Cat.</string>
    <string name="drago_s">The Born of the Dragon has a bold, nonconforming temperament, sometimes even bizarre; This helps them easily conquer the sympathy of others. There is no animal in the Chinese Horoscope of equal thickness; The Dragon is described as ingenious, resolute and persevering in achieving its goals. The natives of the Dragon are naturally involved in leadership, not only in narrow, but even top-level, with the ability to convince entire populations to give them listening and support. The mistake they may incur is to show themselves overly numb and insensitive; I also can not withstand frustration due to failure.</string>
    <string name="snake_s"> The Snake\'s Born is equipped with a savoir-faire that helps them to handle the best of conditions and to get out of trouble. They have a charm to which it is difficult to escape; They are aware of it, so to use it, sometimes with cynicism and little attention to the feelings of others in order to achieve their goals. They have a preference for philosophy. They enjoy it when everything revolves around them. The mistake they may incur is to show little modesty. </string>
    <string name="scimmia_s"> Monkey borns have an inexhaustible energy; For this reason they never stop, and they can not identify their relaxation with it. They are the role of \ "confessors \" within the group of friends, who feel comfortable in confiding, to those who are so listened to, their own problems. They have seduction skills they use to score many achievements; They only come to marry after having lived many stories, making sure that the chosen person will lead their lifestyle. The mistake that the Monkey\'s birth may be in is to lose control, especially after a few more cups. </string>
    <string name="cane_s"> The Dog\'s births are endowed with a sincere and honest indole that puts the foundation of their existence, private as well as working, a very straightforward behavior. If you are sure of their position, the Dogs are struggling with all their strength to expose and assert their opinions without fear. They know how to conquer the trust of friends thanks to the availability and the confidentiality that distinguish them. In listening to those who trust with them, they are generous of good suggestions. The mistake that the Dog\'s birth can cause is that of an excessive social closure and a somewhat cold relationship with his partner. </string>
    <string name="pig_s"> The Boarbirds are provided with a character in the burbero appearance; As knowledge is deeper, however, they know how to outsmart their most kind and friendly talents. What matters most to them is family and friendships. Wild Boars have a strong capacity for attention and concentration that helps them in studying the most difficult sciences, such as physics. Estimators of the good table, are happy to spend the evenings in the company of dearest friends. The mistake that wild boars can inflict on is to get rid of people with their bland and unhelpful approach. </string>
    <string name="aries_s"> Do not go back to an interesting job opportunity. The Moon is in your mark and with its positive influences will make sure everything goes in the best of ways. However, you are only at the beginning of your climb to success. </string>
    <string name="taurus_s"> You are ready to question and open the door to the news, thanks to the presence of Mercury in the sign. This willingness to change will be noticeable at work and you may receive very interesting proposals. </string>
    <string name="gemini_s"> To renounce living a love story for fear will surely put you safe from suffering, but it would also prevent you from growing up and evolving. You are not listening to the Neptune Mermaids in Pisces and look for someone with whom to share something important. </string>
    <string name="cancer_s"> You are caught up with an uncomfortable work situation. The Moon is in a disarmonious look in the sign of the Aries making you nervous and ready to shoot for a none. The real risk is a bad match between colleagues. </string>
    <string name="leo_s"> The presence of the Moon in Aries, jointly with Uranus in the same sign, will wings your projects. You will be thrilling situations and your business will go on swollen sails, especially if you work independently, by freelance professionals. </string>
    <string name="virgo_s"> Neptune in Pisces invites you to dream without paying attention to what is happening around you, exposing you to the risk of big disappointments. Fortunately, though, you have Pluto in Capricorn on your part that reinforces your rationality by making you more wise. </string>
    <string name="libra_s"> The entrance to the Moon in Aries will make things around you going astonished. Feel clearly that the air around you is different but you are not entirely sure of how you are designating certain situations. Time to time, there is no hurry. </string>
    <string name="scorpio_s"> Set aside past uncertainties linked to the past. Dissidious Mercury in Taurus entices your thoughts, pushing you to regret the poured milk. Do not follow this nostalgic state of mind that will only give you melancholy and sorrow. </string>
    <string name="sagi_s"> The Moon and Uranus in Aries make you smile and make you feel full of love to be conveyed to others. Today you will let feelings and feelings flow freely with great enthusiasm. You want news and know how to introduce changes in your life. </string>
    <string name="capri_s"> The presence of the Moon and Uranus in the Aries sign, in a disarming look, will cause you to feel very intense the need to overturn some blocked situations in your favor. If you do not succeed with the good ones, you will pass the bad and will be troubled for everyone! </string>
    <string name="acqua_s"> The Moon and Uranus in the Aries friend sign project you into a very dynamic and productive phase of your life. You are rich in enthusiasm and will make your ideas grow best, both at work and in private life. Surprises will not fail! </string>
    <string name="pisces_s"> Do not go back to an interesting job opportunity. The Moon is in your mark and with its positive influences will make sure everything goes in the best of ways. However, you are only at the beginning of your climb to success. </string>
    <string name="luce_s"> What are the Lizards looking for? Never dome, people born under the moon of Lizard have one rule: never stop, always find something better, make their lives better, always. In the affective world this characteristic ruins many relationships and for the Lizard partners it is never easy to live with this pervasive sense of uncertainty. The main features of the sign are innocence and the ability to donate to others. The profession that best suits their constant need to look for themselves in the world can be, for example, archeology. Many details of their personality are appreciated by those who love freedom. </string>
    <string name="scimmi_m_s"> Pleasant, jolly and always with the smile on the lips: here are presented the born under the Maya sign of the monkey. Very sociable and unhappy they also know they are romantic but often slander of superficiality in the affective world. Another important characteristic of the sign is physical strength and energy, but if not limited, it can lead to major damage that frequently affects themselves. The profession more consistent with Monkey\'s expectations is definitely tied to sport in any form. Although sometimes they may seem a little fussy, these people are very courageous and often motivated by good and honest intentions: they are the paladins of cheerfulness. </string>
    <string name="falco_s"> Fortune always accompanies this sign and who is around it. In fact, the hawk has always been considered sacred to the Maya. Falcon\'s strength lies in its ambitions that are often experienced but equally often achieved. Another characteristic feature of this sign is the great sense of responsibility that is often badly interpreted by others who see it overly apprehensive. The born under the Falcon moon are also reluctant to follow the orders given to them, for their obstinacy they often pay for their sins. The people of this sign often stand out in conceptual and humanistic works. </string>
    <string name="giaguari_s"> Yes, the Jaguars have their ideas, they are often not shared, but they always bring them to the bottom without ever looking back. Great seductors have the ability to put the soul in every story they carry forward. The partner is often surrounded by the aura of these people who bring in all their relationships, even friendship, a strong component of altruism and anger for injustices. The Jaguar\'s sign hates the conditioning and his need for freedom often overcomes everything else, possesses a rebellious soul and is ready for evasion from everyday life. This sign is favored by creativity, social and group work. </string>
    <string name="mcane_s"> Unlike the popular symbolism that sees the fox as a clever and beneficial animal, this sign is by no means conditioned by selfishness and rarely takes advantage of others to fulfill their ends. The Volpi are in fact the people of the mind of the gold always ready to give a hand to those who need it. In the sentimental field they give very few headshots, they love, marry and live happy and happy only love! At all, malicious and with great intuition adore the tranquility, the decorum and the discretion. Very tied to nature are often inclined to choose uncompetitive but of great utility, especially from an ecological or human point of view. </string>
    <string name="snakem_s"> Aesthetic, refined and even a little snob can always emerge for their talents and charm. Very difficult to taste, born under the moon of the Snake, are frequently sought after for their savoir-faire and the irresistible charism. Many people feel seduced and abandoned by this sign despite the fact that there is also strong social intelligence among its features. Never challenging a Snake, putting all the weapons at his disposal, the tendency to prevail is very strong, even in a less ethical but never classy way. If you think the Serpent is all over, then you mean you never faced one! The preferred field by the sign is the fashion and the world of advertising or communication. </string>
    <string name="leprem_s"> The sign of Lepre excels in the art of communication and prevails in all the jobs she is related to as public relations. Active and full of energies hate loneliness: they deprive them of charm. Often with their heads in the clouds they forget important commitments and are amazed if they fail to realize their dreams. Born under this moon give great value to friendship and are often willing to change ideas or to give up compromises to foster the people they want. Tireless optimists always look for a positive reason to move forward, strive for a better future, and this will benefit them in dealing with life. </string>
    <string name="tarta_s"> Professors by nature, Turtles know they are humble and give their knowledge and unconditional help to people around them. They are patient, reflexive and, like the Fox\'s sign, in love strongly prefer stable and lasting relationships. Wise and serene, they have a true passion for the little beauties of life and they also take advantage of the less positive moments to enjoy rest and tranquility. But be careful: this sign is also able to convince you when your values ​​are touched ... patients do, but do not fool yourself or they will be big trouble. </string>
    <string name="pipi_s"> Entrepreneurs of themselves, the "Murcielago" have always been considered "heroic" by the Maya. They are often disconcerting in their attitudes but in them always stands a great balance. They look for and find respect in every context and situation. Very spiritual but concrete in life, both from an economic point of view and from a sentimental point of view. Many Bats are natural leaders, their charisma leads them to deal with every issue with mental strength and high energy. In work stand out for their talents but hardly succeed in accepting subordination, they prefer tasks that ensure autonomy in decisions. </string>
    <string name="scorpiom_s"> Surgery in every decision Maya Scorpions are patient and trained in life. Extremely intelligent from toddlers show their remarkable mental qualities and amaze them with their always sensible reasoning. Born under this moon also possess a great ability not to forget the underworld. This feature makes you realize how much this sign makes you choose to carefully select your friendships. Often closed and timid but with great inner serenity, they are often badly interpreted by those who look at them superficial. In work and in love they are rational and consistent, bringing great serenity to those who attend them. </string>
    <string name="cervo_s"> The main features of the Cervo sign are empathy and the enchanting ability to present yourself to the best. Deer are exceptional people, with great sensibility to others. Sometimes a bit presumptuous and definitely not punctual, they can often bother little patients. And yet it is true that Deer are very tired to accept a sgarro and suffer a lot for their injuries. Do not underestimate the incredible ability to attract this sign that, along with the Jaguars, is the most dangerous sign in terms of couple relationships or in any case sentimental: you can go crazy for a deer! </string>
    <string name="civetta_s"> I kept opening, when the babies born under the moon Maya of the Civetta are absolutely adorable and rich in interesting experiences. Absolutely the most profound and mysterious sign of the Maya horoscope, I am able to perceive thoughts and personalities even with a quick look at people\'s movements and expressions. In love they are initially cold, but they manage to give the best of them when they feel really appreciated and loved. The most relevant works for this sign are those related to the perception of human needs: medicine or psychology. Conquering them is difficult but very satisfying. </string>
    <string name="pavone_s"> Even in Mayan symbolism, the Peacock identifies the people who keep their appearance and always look fit on every occasion. Prophesied to rule but deformed in many behaviors, the born under the sign of the Peacock tend to stand out in society because of their ability to always be at the center of attention. Very passionate in love and able to compete with anyone to get their "prey" many Peacoks have managed to emerge in the world of cinema and entertainment in general. Mostly voted in the art have a strong creative sensibility that Makes it even more attractive and intriguing. </string>
    <string name="melo_s"> Born under the mark of the Apple Tree are endowed with great charisma and lead a life in harmony with nature and with people around them. Their ability to understand and interpret situations makes them able to provide great security to themselves and their friends. Their weak point is the need to gather approval and consent, likely to depress depression. Paradoxically, even though they are endowed with perspicacity and a decisive character, they can crash if their behavior and their choices are not accepted with approval. In love they are very fanciful and love to play the game: their partner will definitely not complain! </string>
    <string name="abete_s"> Fantasy and generosity characterize the spruce born. Especially from children, they need to be able to move in the open to give their energies and creativity free. Once a goal has been identified, they persevere with perseverance at the cost of running the risk. Their weak point consists in nervous shots that can leave people who know them less thoroughly. In love they need security and are usually used to return the partner with a lot of attentions. However, it is not always easy to understand their intentions and their mood to act accordingly. </string>
    <string name="olmo_s"> Perspicacy and altruism are the great virtues of the birth of the Olmos. Optimistic and solar, they prefer to live in the day, avoiding planning in the long run. They are often willing to take important job responsibilities, less willingly in the case of long-term projects. Their weak point is the lack of objectivity in the analysis of some situations: if something does not go as it should, they pretend to do everything but good. In love they are great seducers: bright and extravagant people can easily fascinate their prey. However, they do not like relationships with too many commitments or constraints. </string>
    <string name="cipresso_s"> The Cypress borns are different and nonconventional. Cheerful and brave hate normality and conformism. They want to stand out from the mass with their clothing or their way of seeing things. Often artists or philosophers flee the routine and the monotonous activities. Their weak point is the lack of sensitivity in dealing with some topics with people who may have different values ​​or ways of thinking. In love I am imaginative: even in this franchise they do not like the routine.Solately they are not very trustworthy mates just because they love the changes and the novelties. But they are great amateurs. </string>
    <string name="pioppo_s"> Ambition and passion for risk are two of the main features of poplar births. They do not like the half-measures: everything and immediately could be their motto. Their belief in oneself often involves them in positions of power. Leadership for them is innate. Great managers or clever politicians, they hate banality and mediocrity. Their weak point is the counterattack of their strength: excessive confidence in oneself and in their means. Lack of humility. In love they are demanding and they want a loyal and intelligent partner who knows how to give a lot. There is also a companion who knows how to behave appropriately during worldly events and other social situations to which they often participate. </string>
    <string name="cedro_s"> Adventure and desire for knowledge characterize the births of Cedar. They do not like sedentary jobs, monotonous or without the ability to learn new ideas. They shine in emergency situations or where you need to find an original solution to a problem. Their weak point is the lack of ability to adapt to routine, sometimes inevitable. Sometimes they are also unselfish and think that their tastes are also those of their neighbors. In love they are fanciful and faithful. But woe to them, they will become furious! </string>
    <string name="pino_s"> Born under the sign of Pino are loyal, honest and rational. They do not like sedentary jobs, monotonous or without the ability to learn new ideas. They have great organizational skills and are very precise at work. Their weak point is excessive frothing in some breaches and inability to make decisions in a short time: before deciding they need to weigh all the pros and cons of the various possible choices. In love they are cautious and computers: they do not like excesses and look for a partner who puts security. </string>
    <string name="salix_s"> Love for nature and taste for the challenges are the characteristics of the born under the willow. They prefer work in the open and hate noisy environments. They are very balanced and often for this they achieve excellent results in life. Another positive feature is their tolerance to the next. Sometimes they may tend to pessimism and may be discouraged in the face of their failures. They do not like losing and if they are in difficulty they can not easily recover. In love they are very sensitive and romantic: they love to give more than they can receive. </string>
    <string name="tiglio_s"> Altruistic and sociable, Lime\'s births are the ideal friends. Patience and listening skills are other qualities: for them to gather confidences and to give valuable advice is extremely natural. The Lime borns have an introverted personality and can be very vulnerable in difficult situations. They often demoralize for small problems. In love they are very loyal and tolerant but do not like a partner who wants to impose at all costs. </string>
    <string name="quercia_s"> One day is dedicated to oak: a tree considered by the ancient strong and imposing celtic. The oak born are always loaded with energy and ready to give the best of themselves. Leadership and self-control skills are other positive features of this Celtic sign. Lack of critical sense and self-centeredness are instead the negative sides. In love they are seductive and eager to embody the couple relationship. They are subject to a jealousy crisis. </string>
    <string name="nocciolo_s"> Courage and enthusiasm characterize the Birth of the Nucleus. Lovers of challenges and great fighters: They are very tenacious and before they give up pursuing the set goal they will try them all. Lack of patience with people surround them, selfishness and insensitivity are the downsides. In love they are very enterprising and passionate but do not like being contradicted. </string>
    <string name="corniolo_s"> Dogwood\'s births are independent and idealistic. Enlightened observers and endowed with intelligence beyond the norm, can achieve excellent results in work or politics. They often devote their life to research. Unhappiness for constraints and possible violent attitudes are the negative features. The partner of the born under the Celtic sign of Dogwood must be capable of engaging his companion\'s intellectual faculties and must be able to confront openly. </string>
    <string name="acero_s"> Maple borns are optimistic and perpetual motion. Lovers of distant landscapes are hardly able to adapt to a sedentary life. Numerous companies prefer the attendance of a few trusted friends to share their own experiences. Acacia needs a partner who knows how to support their need for freedom and movement. In return they will provide unrepeatable emotions. </string>
    <string name="noce_s"> Emotions and sensitivity are the two typical characteristics of the born under the Celtic sign of Walnut. Great thinkers and good advisers, I am the ideal friend to trust in your problems. Once they make a decision, they hardly give up their goal. In love they are loyal, passionate and altruistic: the only risk for their partner is to be disappointed by a too routine life. </string>
    <string name="castagno_s"> Energy and leadership skills characterize the born under the Celtic sign of the Chestnut. Lovers of great challenges, they are endowed with determination and perseverance. They often put their skills at the service of the community. In love they need a partner who knows how to drive and advise them. Not loving the half-measures wants a passionate and determined companion who, even if he knows, knows how to make a decision. </string>
    <string name="frassino_s"> The Ashes are unbearable and incorruptible. Their actions follow logic schemes that rarely lead them to making mistakes. Their moral integrity makes them indicated to cover public affairs or positions of responsibility. Lovers of progress, they hate violence and overwhelm. Their weak point is their coldness in interpersonal relationships and lack of sensitivity. The Ash partner must be intelligent and energy-efficient. You will also need to be patient and able to collect your confidences. </string>
    <string name="carpino_s"> Great physical, mental and spiritual resistance: this is the primary characteristic of the born under the Celtic sign of the Hornbeam. Lovers of travel, though accomplished for business purposes, perhaps for business purposes. They have great communication skills that often meet their ambition to emerge. In love they love to dominate the couple relationship but they consider the partner to be the greatest respect: the only risk is that they can not understand all their needs. </string>
    <string name="fico_s"> The figs of the Pike are emotional and sensitive. They often become great artists (actors, writers or painters, for example) or skilled architects. They are able to experience emotions more intense and more than they usually do, and for this reason they are more able to appreciate their natural beauties and artwork. But they are also very vulnerable. The weaker point of the Fico is the excessive sensitivity and fragility at work: they can not be realized in a competitive or sprawling context. Within a competitive environment they fail to assert themselves. Even in love the figs of the fig tree are very sensitive: they appreciate and exchange their attentions and complements but can easily be hurt by a wrong phrase. </string>
    <string name="betulla_s"> Birch\'s born are social and optimistic. They love to be in the company, especially the most dearest friends. The "muzzle" enchants if their cheerfulness is able to make the most pessimistic smile. Their weak point is the lack of autonomy and the inability to work in hostile environments or where social stimuli are lacking. If left alone they suffer and can not find stimuli. In love they do not disdain adventures but when they find the right partner they become loyal and incorruptible. </string>
    <string name="ulivo_s"> One day is dedicated to the Ulivo, September 23, the day of the equinox. Observance and great balance characterize the born under this Celtic sign, intended almost always to achieve success in life. Their weak point is to be overly critical and intolerant. In love they do not like to hasten the times: their partner will have to struggle before they fully conquer their heart and will have to bear moments of apparent coldness and detachment. It will still be worthwhile being patient ... </string>
    <string name="faggio_s"> Energy, strength and enthusiasm characterize the born of the beech that is dedicated to one day, December 22nd. Great leadership skills and desire to fight for noble ideals are the distinctive features of Beech. Their fear of being questioned and accepting changes can make them extremely tedious and conservative. They should try to open themselves to ideas other than theirs and to evaluate things in different ways. Loyalty and devotion characterize them in love where they can bestow on when the relationship consolidates over time. </string>
    <string name="list">Other Birthdays</string>
    <string name="adding">Add new person</string>
    <string name="regN">Do you want to register another person?</string>
    <string name="backT">If you choose not, you will return to the previous menu</string>
    <string name="nope">No!</string>
    <string name="addP">Add!</string>
    <string name="man_woman2">Woman or man?</string>
    <string name="h_arab">Arabic Horoscope</string>
    <string name="i_zod">Zodiac Indu</string>
    <string name="nato_J">Born how many\ndays after Mohammed?</string>
    <string name="pugnale_s">Dagger</string>
    <string name="pugnale">The daggers are champions of honesty and loyalty, but lacking in the very practical sense of diplomacy. For this very reason, they are often in difficult situations caused by the defense of their own ideas in an aggressive way. Because of their innate aggression, they often prefer to be self-employed, as professionals or craftsmen. Exuberance of the born in the dagger is also strong in love affairs, at least until they find the partner who can put his leash.</string>
    <string name="coltellaccio_s">Cutlass</string>
    <string name="coltello_s">Knife</string>
    <string name="kriss_s">Kriss</string>
    <string name="ascia_s">Ax</string>
    <string name="clava_s">Clava</string>
    <string name="mazza_s">Poker</string>
    <string name="catena_s">Chain</string>
    <string name="lancia_s">Launch</string>
    <string name="fionda_s">Slider</string>
    <string name="spada_s">Sword</string>
    <string name="arco_s">Bow</string>
    <string name="coltellaccio">Gentle, orderly, accurate, and tradition-related. From this point of view, the born under the knife sign are real clocks, practically infallible! But do not ask him to be the soul of the party, because from this point of view they are a bit tedious. The ideal jobs for these people are the ones that require great attention or great precision.</string>
    <string name="coltello">Born under this sign, they have a great artistic talent and sensitivity to be able to easily grasp the beauties of nature. Unfortunately, they are uncompetitive to them, so only with many difficulties can emerge as excellence. To counter this, often born under this sign prefer to asceticism. Even in love, they prefer to have a quiet life.</string>
    <string name="kriss">Intuitive intelligence and skills are the basis of the characteristics of the Arab dagger\'s births. Often moody, he is not a simple person to stand next to, though from a sentimental point of view he is very loyal and passionate. A problem for the births of this sign is ambition, which often leads them to have goals not at their reach.</string>
    <string name="ascia">Confident in the next and always optimistic, born under the ax is a dreamer that often finds itself out of reality. To help them are friends, with whom they are able to establish a relationship of mutual trust and respect. Of great artistic tastes, it is easy to find an ax of the ax that can break through this field. From a sentimental point of view, they are not passionate amateurs but tend to fascinate with their refinement.</string>
    <string name="clava">Born under this sign are calm and precise people. At the limit of the maniac, so much to be uncomfortable when unforeseen events occur. Lovers of peace prefer a quiet life to a constant and tiring quest for ambitions. Big table fans with friends, for this reason, tend to be very fat.</string>
    <string name="mazza">Extraversed and brave, iron-markers also have great adaptation skills. This leads them to put in their favor any kind of situation even though this sometimes leads to inconsistencies. With these features, the bachelor\'s nines are indicated for trade and communication professions. From an affective point of view, they are loyal and loyal to the family, better if it is large.</string>
    <string name="catena">True diplomats. This is the best definition for the born of the chain. Ability to take advantage of the situations they are, they are real lovers of beautiful and expensive items. This leads them to look for jobs that are based on the relationship with the public and pay salaries. The partner of the born under this sign must also be lovers of luxury and wealth, because in any case they will be surrounded by this situation.</string>
    <string name="lancia">Prudent and brilliant, the lance of the lance always prefers to walk the same length as the leg, convinced that a person of his abilities can succeed without risking to emerge from the others. Simpatic and affable, he simply succeeds in making friends. It must be stimulated as little active and courageous in a loving environment.</string>
    <string name="fionda">Ready to fight against the injustices in the world and true exponents of divergent thinking. From this point of view are people who do not accept compromises and are ready to defend their ideals at all costs. Even in personal relationships, the born of the sling are passionate and idealistic.</string>
    <string name="spada">Swords born are born leaders, they have all the features that could lead them to the vertex, namely charisma, perfectionism, pride, and grin. Always willing to get in the middle of the scene, even in situations where there might be more important people than them or that it would be wiser to defile. Their ambition leads them not to throw too much forward but rather to evaluate situations calmly. This feature accompanies them in every field, including the sentimental one.</string>
    <string name="arco">Intelligent and rational, the bow born faces all his life leaning on his mental abilities. On the one hand this leads him to make good progress in every situation, while keeping him away from ordinary people, who see in his preparation a source of difficulty in establishing a relationship. The bowman must therefore seek to find a compromise potion to relate to the others above all because, in any case, he is a lover of good companies.</string>
    <string name="ariete2">Mesha-Angaraka</string>
    <string name="toro2">Vrishasca-Surkra</string>
    <string name="gemelli2">Mithuna-Budha</string>
    <string name="cancro2">Kataka-Chandra</string>
    <string name="leone2">Simaha-Ravi</string>
    <string name="vergine2">Kanta-Budha</string>
    <string name="bilancia2">Thula-Sukra</string>
    <string name="scorpione2">Vrischica-Angaraka</string>
    <string name="saggittario2">Dhanus-Brishaspati</string>
    <string name="capricorno2">Makara-Sani</string>
    <string name="acquario2">Kumbha-Kethu</string>
    <string name="pesci2">Meena-Galika</string>
    <string name="aries2_s">In Hindu culture, \"Mescha\" represents the focus of the fire. He may not be able to ask, but his sincerity is greatly appreciated. Passionate, dominant, can also be overpowering. Eternal children and men, dissatisfied with their present. In India they claim that these natives aspire to protect, even exaggeratedly, the people beside him. If they may be able to deal with the problems of others becoming possessive until they reach what they want to achieve. This attitude stems from the fact that they do not know how to handle the terms that coexistence and diplomacy demand from everyday life.</string>
    <string name="taurus2_s">The earthy appearance of \"Vrishasca\" is very much heartened for its depth rather than its brilliance. The sense of ownership drives them to the struggle and all their effort is oriented to succeeding in gaining the well-being. The Hindus thought that if they were not able to get their possessions, their frustrations would be very mortifying. They have a lot of inner strength and can be placed in the category of those who are not afraid to face life. When they fail to resolve situations, their aggression might lead to serious internal struggles. Other important goals that one might set out to achieve are to conquer their rights and those of their loved ones.</string>
    <string name="gemini2_s">The \"Mithuna\" are full of initiatives, idealistic and do not fear to face reality. For them affection must manifest themselves with force, which is why they are looking for a determined partner. They belong to the category of lovers of everything, they are passionate and when they decide to do something, nothing and no one will be able to make him change their minds. Hindus argue that there is no duality attributed to Western astrology. As good exponents of air, they seek with anxiety the wealth that only a good friendship can offer them.</string>
    <string name="cancer2_s">The Kataka, are symbolized by the water element, and have a noble appreciation for feelings and love. They live in search of new emotions, they are very sensitive and they take it for nothing. They are looking for great doses of affection, understanding and caresses. Some psychologists consider this affective need as a synonym of weakness, but for astrology, such introversion is only apparent. They need protection and try to outline their intuitive skills and those who are next to them.</string>
    <string name="leo2_s">The \"Simaha\" are leder par excellence. For the Hindus, this sign is a real blend because, on the one hand, they think they are respectful of the rules, but on the other hand they consider them innovative and capable of using great practical sense. The presence of the Leo fire confirms to these natives the practical and natural sense of competence. One of the indisputable features is its great fortune. Even though they always give the feeling of running behind fantasy, their existence is constantly struggling to find solutions in the real world.</string>
    <string name="virgo2_s">\"Kanta\", the Hindu philosophy, are categorized as those that depict the lives of large tracts without outlining with their strokes the little details. Even if they know more than any other nuances, their nature urges them to focus their mind on the great works. they face life with spirit of the game, not knowing how to live alone, tend to be a large family. they can be masters of their own in spite fate of contrasts, for this reason always know how to find The right solutions, like touched by a magic wand.</string>
    <string name="libra2_s">In India, with or without philosophical reason, they are convinced that the Thula trend emerges at any time. They have such a personality that principles and goals are highly valued. They are smart, strategic. In India, the western scale represents the sensitivity, the deleitante, the one who must reach a high level. When they impose a goal it is difficult to divert them because their intransigence is known. Mahatma Gandhi belonged to this sign.</string>
    <string name="scorpio2_s">The Hindus asserted that the Vrischica symbolize constant emotions. They also claim that, to learn life, they had to fall and rise several times. Only after several strokes their existence grows stronger than ever. These natives always react to the external stimulus, wanting to live intensely all. Understanding will always be little for their needs. Their ambitions concentrate on distinguishing themselves from the pile, thus gaining recognition for their creative and detached personality.</string>
    <string name="sagi2_s">Inexhaustible personality. The Hindus regarded them as possessing astral resources. Dhanus is an intellectual source of resources. They pursue fate without waste any opportunity. Capable of managing any activity, especially in what is related to art and creativity. They have very good taste as well as a great wit. These qualities, combined with their enormous self-critique, will bring them up to envied places, both in material and affective things.</string>
    <string name="capri2_s">Makara, according to Hindu philosophy, encloses within themselves the absolute and vigilant control of their desires and ambitions. They are the ones that demand the full availability of their friendships and their partners. In India it is said that native people under this sign suffer a lot because they trust too much about who is next to them but because of their intuition and intelligence they can see beyond and be so well guided through their ideas. Although he is the last "cardinal ground", they belong to the mental type as well as being suitable climate researchers. They are worthy of admiration.</string>
    <string name="acqua2_s">According to the Hindus, the Kumbha are alert, secure and independent. They are leaders, leaders, and they have great influence over others. Their performance is such that many times they act for others, leaving their own interests apart. They are good organizers. Their standard of living is outside of common things and their will makes their destiny trace. Those who can not understand them are rare and impenetrable people. They are predestined to enrich the existence of many, for this reason always seek someone with whom to share everything.</string>
    <string name="pisces2_s">Thanks to the influence of the planets in its conjunction, the personality "Meena emerges for an efficient, creative and revitalizing temperament. Hindus felt that their will needed to be strengthened for the trust that was dispensed to. They are called to enrich the life of others and predestined to emerge in the artistic and diplomatic life, if they wish. In a sense, it is a life spent at the service of the neighbor.</string >
    <string name="season">Birth Season</string>
    <string name="di">Of</string>
    <string name="addPeopele">Add People</string>
    <string name="horror_t">Normal or horror Horoscop?</string>
    <string name="prefs_title_visual">Theme</string>
    <string name="love">Unlock love modality?</string>
    <string name="love_t">Love or not?</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="enter_your_crush_name">Enter your crush name</string>
    <string name="calculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="no_field">Please fill both the fields</string>
    <string name="love1">The love between</string>
    <string name="love2">and</string>
    <string name="love3">is</string>
    <string name="love4">%</string>
    <string name="scelta_h">What horoscope to see?</string>
    <string name="change">Where do you want to go?</string>
    <string name="changeT">Select the option you prefer</string>
    <string name="nopeC">Birthday\'s List</string>
    <string name="addC">Main Menu</string>
</resources>
